

# Kenrick Frans Robin Halff Curriculum Vitae

A software developer models the real world to solve real problems and create a fitting and accessible interface. Technology has exploded past decades and we don't know how to evolve with it. My mission is to solve problems, not causing them. Listening, understanding, testing and learning is the best way to achieve this.

- > Contact kenrickhalff@gmail.com
- > Portfolio kenrickhalff-com.vercel.app
- > Born November 5th 1993

 $NaN \neq NaN \neq NaN \neq NaN \neq NaN \neq NaN \neq NaN$ 

# **EDUCATION**

# > MBO Utrecht Media

Application, Media & Game Development 2012 - 2016 MBO Niveau 4

## > Hogeschool Utrecht

HBO Applied Computer Science 2018 - 2019

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### > Logaholic BV

Ellermanstraat 15, 1099 BW Amsterdam Stagiaire / Junior Web Developer 2013 - 2014

- Data visualization
- Magento 1 store with integrated subscription options

## > Bizzmark

Vreeswijksestraatweg 22, 3432 NA Nieuwegein Stagiaire / Junior Fullstack Developer 2014 - 2015 & 2016

- Custom WordPress themes & design
- MyBizzMail, made with React, Redux & Node/Express rest API

# **NOTABLE WORK**

## > Websites / Apps

<u>kenrickhalff-com.vercel.app</u> <u>casual-happiness.vercel.com</u> <u>vnfkd.nl</u>

#### > Games

<u>kennyomg.itch.io/corona-shopper</u> JBL Speaker Catcher

## > Jouw Omgeving

Maliebaan 79, 3581 CG Utrecht React Developer 2015 - 2016

 Worked on Jouw Omgeving tools in Django & React

## > Comsys & Livecom

Laan Blussé van Oud Alblas 2a, 3769 AT Soesterberg Javascript Developer 01 02 2017 - 01 09 2017

- Angular 1 & Java Spring
- Modernizing old web interfaces (Comsys Dashboard, Livecom webchat & knowledgebank
- Research & consultancy for new development in tech

# **SKILLS**

## > Languages

TS, JS, Python, C++, C#, PHP, Java, SQL, GraphQL, FaunaQL

#### > Framework / Engine

React, Next, WP, Express, Django, Unity3d, Phalcon, SFML

## > Professional

OOP, FP, UX, TDD, Agile, Scrum, Lean

## > Social Brothers

Europalaan 100, 3526 KS Utrecht Frontend Developer 09 10 2019 - 30 06 2020

- Building and maintaining custom WordPress themes.
- E-commerce & SEO

# > Casual Development

Lage Naarderweg 28B, 1211 AB Hilversum Founder

04 04 2018 - Now

- Psychology driven
- Lean Startup
- Gamification with the Octalysis Framework
- Nextls, Typescript & FaunaDB
- TDD